<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>sndbx.be - Emiliano Izquierdo</title><link href="https://sndbx.be/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://sndbx.be/feeds/emiliano-izquierdo.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://sndbx.be/</id><updated>2019-08-06T21:27:54+02:00</updated><entry><title>Hello, internet</title><link href="https://sndbx.be/writing/hello-internet/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-08-06T21:27:54+02:00</published><updated>2019-08-06T21:27:54+02:00</updated><author><name>Emiliano Izquierdo</name></author><id>tag:sndbx.be,2019-08-06:/writing/hello-internet/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Lacandon jungle" src="../../static/articles/01_hello-internet/img/DSC_0777-001.JPG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p class="wide mono dim small float-left"&gt;&lt;img alt="Lacandon jungle" src="https://sndbx.be/static/articles/01_hello-internet/img/DSC_0777-001.JPG"&gt;
Road to Lacandon jungle in southern Mexico, January 2019&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="drop-cap"&gt;S&lt;/span&gt;ince a couple of months I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking of retiring from social-media platforms like Facebook, Twitter&amp;hellip; you name it. The truth is that letting them go has been quite a hassle. They have become very practical tools to keep in contact with family, friends and freetime interests, all in one place. They have also become an important source of news and information. I&amp;rsquo;ve profited and experienced them in very positive ways, however, as an avalanche of marketing and privacy concerns continues to grow, their intrusiveness has already outweighed their benefit. Added to this, the amount of misinformation imposes a high price on the time required to cherry-pick the relevant stuff. Moreover, the prevasiveness of fake news might as well be affecting us in ways we do not concioussly recognize.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going cold turkey might not be the best current solution to the social-media paradox. However, perhaps by adopting a gradual and more constructive strategy will, if not effectivley, at least more creatively balance out their requirement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog is aimed at keeping an internet presence while adding a little more custom and non-intrusive look at stuff that I like and do. I hope that by doing so, in the future I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to disregard social-media while gaining some skills at writing.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="internet"></category><category term="social media"></category></entry></feed>