<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>sndbx.be - Emiliano Izquierdo</title><link href="https://sndbx.be/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://sndbx.be/feeds/emiliano-izquierdo.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://sndbx.be/</id><updated>2019-08-13T00:00:00+02:00</updated><entry><title>Slovenian summer</title><link href="https://sndbx.be/photos/slovenian-summer/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-08-13T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2019-08-13T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Emiliano Izquierdo</name></author><id>tag:sndbx.be,2019-08-13:/photos/slovenian-summer/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="mono"&gt;&lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/02_heidelberg/img/DSC_0426.JPG"&gt;There is nothing special, or there might not be anything special about Heidelberg. It might very well be...&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;ul class="Grid Grid--gutters Grid--full large-Grid--fit wide"&gt;

        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/02_heidelberg/img/DSC_0426.JPG"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;
         &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/02_heidelberg/img/DSC_0426.JPG"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;
         &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/02_heidelberg/img/DSC_0426.JPG"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;      
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ul class="Grid Grid--gutters Grid--full large-Grid--fit wide"&gt;
        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/02_heidelberg/img/DSC_0426.JPG"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;
         &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/02_heidelberg/img/DSC_0426.JPG"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ul class="Grid Grid--gutters Grid--full large-Grid--1of3 wide"&gt;

        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/02_heidelberg/img/DSC_0426.JPG"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;
         &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/02_heidelberg/img/DSC_0426.JPG"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;
         &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/02_heidelberg/img/DSC_0426.JPG"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;      
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><category term="outdoor"></category><category term="travel"></category></entry><entry><title>Ha-jo! Heidelberg</title><link href="https://sndbx.be/writing/ha-jo-heidelberg/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-08-06T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2019-08-06T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Emiliano Izquierdo</name></author><id>tag:sndbx.be,2019-08-06:/writing/ha-jo-heidelberg/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="mono"&gt;&lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/02_heidelberg/img/DSC_0426.JPG"&gt;There is nothing special, or there might not be anything special about Heidelberg. It might very well be...&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p class="wide mono dim"&gt;&lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="https://sndbx.be/static/articles/writing/02_heidelberg/img/DSC_0426.JPG"&gt;
Old bridge, Heidelberg October 2013&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="wide"&gt;&lt;span class="drop-cap"&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;here is nothing special, or there might not be anything special about Heidelberg. It might very well be, that the city, and its ihabitants and whatever surrounds &lt;em&gt;the city&lt;/em&gt;, makes up for just another good example of a german university town. However, for me Heidelberg happens to be a very special place. I like to believe that the city is composed of a well balanced mixture of many small but enjoyable details. Each of those tiny pieces arranged together in a configuration that makes a truely livable city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="sidenote sans dim framed"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ha-jo!&lt;/em&gt; is the &lt;em&gt;Narrenruff&lt;/em&gt; in Heidelberg. This celebration calling is shouted out loud during the street parade and the &lt;em&gt;Fastnacht&lt;/em&gt; (carnival) festivities to demonstrate an expression of a joyfull spirit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The city is small. Take your bike and ride to every corner with ease. Up and down the Königstuhl, pass the Weststadt, through Plöck and into the city center. Take a view of the city from across the old bridge, go and catch fresh air, leave the bike and climb up the Philosophenweg and hike into the woods. Visit and take some pictures of the Thingstätte. Go back down to town and enjoy a coffee at the market square in Neuenheim. Feeling like doing some sport, have a run along the Neckar. If not, just sit next to the Neckar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="sidenote sans dim framed"&gt;Few places are like Heidelberg. Every time I go and visit other places I end up missing this city and I&amp;rsquo;m always really happy when I return. It has become a good reference for me to assess how much I&amp;rsquo;d be willing to move to another city&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="mono dim"&gt;&lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="https://sndbx.be/static/articles/writing/02_heidelberg/img/DSC_0427.JPG"&gt;
Heidelberg castle, October 2013&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ha-jo!&lt;/em&gt; - Whithout a notice, it&amp;rsquo;s been almost 8 years since I arrived to Heidelberg. Here I studied a Master and a PhD. Here I&amp;rsquo;ve met a lot of my current friends. Through them I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten to learn about the cultures of various countries and I have been nourrished from their friendships. Through living here I&amp;rsquo;ve also learned the European and the German mindsets which I have assimilated and incorporated into my personality. Here I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced many things for the first time and I&amp;rsquo;ve had memorable moments that for sure will be long lasting. Here it feels like home. It&amp;rsquo;s difficult not to think how much I&amp;rsquo;m going to miss this city once I have to leave.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="mono dim"&gt;&lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="https://sndbx.be/static/articles/writing/02_heidelberg/img/DSC_0318.JPG"&gt;
Heiligenberg, Heidelberg October 2013&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="heidelberg"></category><category term="living"></category></entry><entry><title>Hello, internet</title><link href="https://sndbx.be/writing/hello-internet/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-08-01T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2019-08-01T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Emiliano Izquierdo</name></author><id>tag:sndbx.be,2019-08-01:/writing/hello-internet/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="mono"&gt;&lt;img alt="Lacandon jungle" src="../../static/articles/writing/01_hello-internet/img/DSC_0777-001.JPG"&gt;Since a couple of months I've been thinking of retiring from social-media platforms like Facebook, Twitter... you name it...&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p class="wide mono dim"&gt;&lt;img alt="Lacandon jungle" src="https://sndbx.be/static/articles/writing/01_hello-internet/img/DSC_0777-001.JPG"&gt;
Road to Lacandon jungle in southern Mexico, January 2019&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="drop-cap"&gt;S&lt;/span&gt;ince a couple of months I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking of retiring from social-media platforms like Facebook, Twitter&amp;hellip; you name it. The truth is that letting them go has been quite a hassle. They have become very practical tools to keep in contact with family, friends and freetime interests, all in one place. They have also become an important source of news and information. I&amp;rsquo;ve profited and experienced them in very positive ways, however, as an avalanche of marketing and privacy concerns continues to grow, their intrusiveness has already outweighed their benefit. Added to this, the amount of misinformation imposes a high price on the time required to cherry-pick the relevant stuff. Moreover, the prevasiveness of fake news might as well be affecting us in ways we do not concioussly recognize.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going cold turkey might not be the best current solution to the social-media paradox. However, perhaps by adopting a gradual and more constructive strategy will, if not effectivley, at least more creatively balance out their requirement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog is aimed at keeping an internet presence while adding a little more custom and non-intrusive look at stuff that I like and do. I hope that by doing so, in the future I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to disregard social-media while gaining some skills at writing.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="internet"></category><category term="social media"></category></entry></feed>