<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>sndbx.be - Emiliano Izquierdo</title><link href="https://sndbx.be/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://sndbx.be/feeds/emiliano-izquierdo.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://sndbx.be/</id><updated>2019-09-03T00:00:00+02:00</updated><entry><title>Kerokuro</title><link href="https://sndbx.be/pottery/kerokuro/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-09-03T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2019-09-03T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Emiliano Izquierdo</name></author><id>tag:sndbx.be,2019-09-03:/pottery/kerokuro/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="mono"&gt;&lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/DSC_0166.JPG"&gt;A kerokuro is a Japanese traditional pottery wheel. Earlier this year I got to build one myself ... &lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p class="wide mono dim"&gt;&lt;img alt="kerokuro" src="https://sndbx.be/static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/DSC_0166.JPG"&gt;
At home in Guanajuato, Mexico March 2019&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="wide"&gt;&lt;span class="drop-cap"&gt;E&lt;/span&gt;arlier last year (2018) I got to learn pottery and ceramics. What started to be a simple experiment where I would make a pinch pot &amp;ndash;one time a bowl, one other time a cup&amp;ndash; pottery rapidly developed into a serious hobby; perhaps a temporal obsession. Early during the discovery process, I got to watch all the &lt;a href="https://www.goldmarkart.com/ceramics"&gt;Goldmark Gallery&lt;/a&gt; videos featuring well known potters as they are Lisa Hammond, Phil Rogers, Anne Mette Hjortshøj, Ken Matsuzaki among many others. Soon I was hooked, every video was charged with beauty. Every time I would watch a video, I would get more and more trapped into the handcrafting process, and also into imagining my way into more advanced pottery techniques. First, it was throwing on the wheel, later it was developing my own glazes, another time it would be learning a different firing method.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="wide"&gt;This time it was about pottery wheels. It was precisely on &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QLYivjLbWxg"&gt;Ken Matsuzaki&amp;rsquo;s video&lt;/a&gt; where I got to see him throwing chawan teabowls on a wooden pottery kick-wheel or &lt;em&gt;kerokuro&lt;/em&gt; (&lt;code&gt;蹴ろくろ&lt;/code&gt;) as it is called in Japanese or &lt;em&gt;balmulle&lt;/em&gt; (&lt;code&gt;발물레&lt;/code&gt;) in Korean. The take was an enjoyable feature of craftsmanship, and at its center there was the traditional Japanese wooden kerokuro.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class="Grid Grid--gutters Grid--full large-Grid--fit wide"&gt;
        &lt;li class="Grid-cell" style="position:relative;"&gt;
        &lt;!-- &lt;li class="Grid-cell" style="position:relative;"&gt; --&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/DSC_0187.JPG"&gt;
            &lt;!-- &lt;div  class = "sans" style="position:absolute; bottom:1em; left: 1.5em; font-weight:bold"&gt;A&lt;/div&gt; --&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;
         &lt;!-- &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/DSC_0178.JPG"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt; --&gt;
        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/DSC_0170.JPG"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ul class="Grid Grid--gutters Grid--full large-Grid--fit wide"&gt;

        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/DSC_0171.JPG"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;
         &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/DSC_0188.JPG"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ul class="Grid Grid--gutters Grid--full large-Grid--fit wide"&gt;

        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
           &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/DSC_0173.JPG"&gt;

       &lt;/li&gt;  
       &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
          &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/DSC_0175.JPG"&gt;

       &lt;/li&gt;



&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p class="wide mono dim"&gt;Detailed views of the kerokuro&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="float-left"&gt;The kerokuro is in essence very simple; it is made of two parts. The flying wheel which is a single piece completely made of wood, and the fixed base which is a metal plate soldered to a shaft. The flying wheel is composed of a bottom kick wheel and top turntable. These are joined through four wooden poles that transmit the work of the kick from the bottom to the top. The flying wheel is suspended onto the shaft and relies on a pin and a cup system to rotate, whereby a pin is fixed at the bottom of the turntable, and a receiving cup which is drilled on the top end of the shaft. While this is enough to provide the full functionality of the wheel, the overall stability is further enhanced by a flange bearing attached to the bottom wheel. This ball bearing constrains the lateral movement of the wheel and helps maintaining the rotation around the vertical axis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="dim sidenote framed sans"&gt;Technical note: there are other assembly setups where instead of a pin and cup system, a flange bearing is used on the top turntable. While such a setup simplifies the construction of the flying wheel, it requires extra work on the shaft, as it has to be partially lathe-cut to provide an offset onto which the flange bearing will sit. Moreover, in such a scenario, the load distribution is not appropriate for a flange bearing: which is designed for supporting radial loads. A better fit would be to use an angular contact ball-bearing or a tappered roller-bearing which would play well with both the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bearing_(mechanical)#Loads"&gt;axial and radial loads&lt;/a&gt; generated during the turning of the wheel. In addition, they would balance the loads to better maintain the angular momentum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="clear: left;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ul class="Grid Grid--gutters Grid--1of2"&gt;
        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/plan1.jpg"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
           &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/plan2.jpg"&gt;

       &lt;/li&gt;  
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p class="mono dim" style="line-height:1em"&gt;Sketch of the design. Left: rough measurements for the wheel head and the shaft. Right: pin and cup measurements&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="sans wide"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Last year, I got to build a kerokuro from scratch. From plain wood beams until its functioning state were a the end of the day I would throw some pots on it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="wide"&gt;The journey of building a kerokuro began with the design. Despite the simplicity of the mechanism, the precise construction of the artifact required a couple of considerations. The availability and selection of wood, the tools at hand, the access to expert knowledge. These were factors that could either make it easier or harder to carry out the project to its best possible outcome. After a thorough internet research where only a couple of blog posts with little details where available (I also translate-searched Japanese websites), I managed to get a rough idea of which important design decisions had to be made, the rest, I kind of eye-balled it from pictures found on the internet, or figured it out myself during the building process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="wide"&gt;To begin with the construction, one has to determine which kind of wood would be readily available and at the same time satisfy the purpose of a pottery wheel. From the one end, the wood is going to be in constant contact with water, from the other end it will provide the momentum upon which the clay will get its shape after being pressed against. Thus, it has to be a wood that responds well to water and which is very dense (heavy) as to maintain a strong angular momentum. Unfortunately, to find such characteristics in a wood is not that easy, unless you have a wood handler specialized in hardwoods. In the sawmill near my hometown neighborhood I was lucky I could find &lt;em&gt;encino&lt;/em&gt;, a local type of oak of the &lt;em&gt;Quercus&lt;/em&gt; genus with a reddish coloration. Encino wood is very heavy and it also behaves well in contact with water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class="Grid Grid--gutters Grid--1of3 wide"&gt;
        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/beams1.jpg"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
           &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/beams2.jpg"&gt;

       &lt;/li&gt;  
       &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
          &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/beams3.jpg"&gt;

      &lt;/li&gt;  
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ul class="Grid Grid--gutters Grid--1of3 wide"&gt;
        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/gluing1.jpg"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
           &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/gluing2.jpg"&gt;

       &lt;/li&gt;  
       &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
          &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/gluing3.jpg"&gt;

      &lt;/li&gt;  
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p class="mono dim wide" style="line-height:1em;"&gt;First steps into the construction: assembly of thick wood plates from encino beams&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the sawmill I was lucky I could gather some encino beams of 6x12cm, some beams of 6x6cm and some smaller rods which would serve as the posts (~5x5cm). What I did afterwards was to cut the beams in various pieces of 39cm in length, then, by combining these resulting beam segments (6x12x39cm and 6x6x39cm) together, I planed them flat and glue them together into four cuboids of around 6x39x39cm. Afterwards, I sanded them and again I glued two of the cuboids together for the top turntable and the other two for the bottom kickwheel. Before being glued, tablehe two cuboids for the bottom wheel also required having a ~5cm hole drilled in them as to allow the shaft to pass through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class="Grid Grid--gutters Grid--1of3 wide"&gt;
        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/round_cut1.jpg"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
           &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/round_cut2.jpg"&gt;

       &lt;/li&gt;  
       &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
          &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/round_cut3.jpg"&gt;

      &lt;/li&gt;  
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ul class="Grid Grid--gutters Grid--1of3 wide"&gt;
        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/shaft3.jpg"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
           &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/shaft1.jpg"&gt;

       &lt;/li&gt;  
       &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
          &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/shaft2.jpg"&gt;

      &lt;/li&gt;  
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p class="mono dim wide" style="line-height:1em;"&gt;Top: Cutting the cuboids into wheels. Bottom: Design of the base and the base&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="wide"&gt;The next steps involved the cutting of the two glued blocks into the wheels. For this I required some extra help. I am lucky to be cousin with Hernán, a very talented carpenter. From him I could get the proper tools and learn form his expertise during the building process. He also helped me throughout the assembly. We cut the two blocks with a band saw and drilled 1 inch holes to fit each of the four posts. Additionally, we drilled an extra 1 inch hole at the bottom center of the top turntable. This allowed to fit the pin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="wide"&gt;Once all pieces were assembled, and before I could throw my first pieces in it, I gave the kerokuro a finish with Danish oil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="wide"&gt;
&lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/04_kerokuro/img/DSC_0067.JPG"&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class="mono dim wide" style="line-height:1em;"&gt;The almost finished kerokuro at Hernán's workshop&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- margin-left: 200px; --&gt;

&lt;!-- /* margin-left: calc(0.94rem + 510px + 225px - 900px); */ --&gt;

&lt;!-- margin-right: calc(0.94rem + 510px - 730px); --&gt;</content><category term="ceramics"></category><category term="DIY"></category><category term="woodwork"></category></entry><entry><title>Summer in Slovenia</title><link href="https://sndbx.be/photos/summer-in-slovenia/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-08-13T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2019-08-13T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Emiliano Izquierdo</name></author><id>tag:sndbx.be,2019-08-13:/photos/summer-in-slovenia/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="mono"&gt;&lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/03_slovenia/img/DSC_0516-001.JPG"&gt;Dusting off some old pictures. This time I got to remember a trip to Slovenia...&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p class="wide mono dim"&gt;&lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="https://sndbx.be/static/articles/writing/03_slovenia/img/DSC_0516-001.JPG"&gt;
Somewhere, Triglav National Park, Slovenia August 2016&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="drop-cap"&gt;R&lt;/span&gt;ecently, and with the idea of bringing a bit of order in the chaos that lately rules our day to day lifes, I got to engage in the seemingly impossible task of organizing my pictures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Notably, I have always made an effort to bring my camera with me to partially document my trips, and thus, a considerable amount of pictures have been accumulating without receiving any further attention, they have been abandoned. Bunches of pictures ignored despite the invested diligent effort.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the intent of dusting off some of my old pictures, I&amp;rsquo;ll be selecting a couple to publish them in this blog. To start with, here are some pictures of Slovenia taken some four years ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class="Grid Grid--gutters Grid--full large-Grid--fit wide"&gt;
        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/03_slovenia/img/DSC_0504-001.JPG"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;
         &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/03_slovenia/img/DSC_0509-001.JPG"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ul class="Grid Grid--gutters Grid--1of3 wide"&gt;

        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/03_slovenia/img/DSC_0510-001.JPG"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;
         &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/03_slovenia/img/DSC_0496-001.JPG"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;
         &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/03_slovenia/img/DSC_0517-001.JPG"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;      
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ul class="Grid Grid--gutters Grid--full large-Grid--1of2 wide"&gt;
&lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
   &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/03_slovenia/img/DSC_0576-001.JPG"&gt;

&lt;/li&gt;

        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/03_slovenia/img/DSC_0616-001.JPG"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;



&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ul class="Grid Grid--gutters Grid--1of3 wide"&gt;

&lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
    &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/03_slovenia/img/DSC_0502-001.JPG"&gt;

&lt;/li&gt;

        &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/03_slovenia/img/DSC_0518-001.JPG"&gt;

        &lt;/li&gt;
         &lt;li class="Grid-cell"&gt;
            &lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/03_slovenia/img/DSC_0528-001.JPG"&gt;
        &lt;/li&gt;


&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p class="wide mono dim"&gt;&lt;img alt="Slovenia" src="https://sndbx.be/static/articles/writing/03_slovenia/img/DSC_0592-001.JPG"&gt;
Krn, Triglav National Park, Slovenia August 2016&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="outdoor"></category><category term="travel"></category></entry><entry><title>Ha-jo! Heidelberg</title><link href="https://sndbx.be/writing/ha-jo-heidelberg/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-08-06T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2019-08-06T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Emiliano Izquierdo</name></author><id>tag:sndbx.be,2019-08-06:/writing/ha-jo-heidelberg/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="mono"&gt;&lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="../../static/articles/writing/02_heidelberg/img/DSC_0426.JPG"&gt;There is nothing special, or there might not be anything special about Heidelberg. It might very well be...&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p class="wide mono dim"&gt;&lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="https://sndbx.be/static/articles/writing/02_heidelberg/img/DSC_0426.JPG"&gt;
Old bridge, Heidelberg October 2013&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="wide"&gt;&lt;span class="drop-cap"&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;here is nothing special, or there might not be anything special about Heidelberg. It might very well be, that the city, and its ihabitants and whatever surrounds &lt;em&gt;the city&lt;/em&gt;, makes up for just another good example of a german university town. However, for me Heidelberg happens to be a very special place. I like to believe that the city is composed of a well balanced mixture of many small but enjoyable details. Each of those tiny pieces arranged together in a configuration that makes a truely livable city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="sidenote sans dim framed"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ha-jo!&lt;/em&gt; is the &lt;em&gt;Narrenruff&lt;/em&gt; in Heidelberg. This celebration calling is shouted out loud during the street parade and the &lt;em&gt;Fastnacht&lt;/em&gt; (carnival) festivities to demonstrate an expression of a joyfull spirit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The city is small. Take your bike and ride to every corner with ease. Up and down the Königstuhl, pass the Weststadt, through Plöck and into the city center. Take a view of the city from across the old bridge, go and catch fresh air, leave the bike and climb up the Philosophenweg and hike into the woods. Visit and take some pictures of the Thingstätte. Go back down to town and enjoy a coffee at the market square in Neuenheim. Feeling like doing some sport, have a run along the Neckar. If not, just sit next to the Neckar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="sidenote sans dim framed"&gt;Few places are like Heidelberg. Every time I go and visit other places I end up missing this city and I&amp;rsquo;m always really happy when I return. It has become a good reference for me to assess how much I&amp;rsquo;d be willing to move to another city&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="mono dim"&gt;&lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="https://sndbx.be/static/articles/writing/02_heidelberg/img/DSC_0427.JPG"&gt;
Heidelberg castle, October 2013&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ha-jo!&lt;/em&gt; - Whithout a notice, it&amp;rsquo;s been almost 8 years since I arrived to Heidelberg. Here I studied a Master and a PhD. Here I&amp;rsquo;ve met a lot of my current friends. Through them I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten to learn about the cultures of various countries and I have been nourrished from their friendships. Through living here I&amp;rsquo;ve also learned the European and the German mindsets which I have assimilated and incorporated into my personality. Here I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced many things for the first time and I&amp;rsquo;ve had memorable moments that for sure will be long lasting. Here it feels like home. It&amp;rsquo;s difficult not to think how much I&amp;rsquo;m going to miss this city once I have to leave.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="mono dim"&gt;&lt;img alt="Heidelberg" src="https://sndbx.be/static/articles/writing/02_heidelberg/img/DSC_0318.JPG"&gt;
Heiligenberg, Heidelberg October 2013&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="heidelberg"></category><category term="living"></category></entry><entry><title>Hello, internet</title><link href="https://sndbx.be/writing/hello-internet/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-08-01T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2019-08-01T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Emiliano Izquierdo</name></author><id>tag:sndbx.be,2019-08-01:/writing/hello-internet/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="mono"&gt;&lt;img alt="Lacandon jungle" src="../../static/articles/writing/01_hello-internet/img/DSC_0777-001.JPG"&gt;Since a couple of months I've been thinking of retiring from social-media platforms like Facebook, Twitter... you name it...&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p class="wide mono dim"&gt;&lt;img alt="Lacandon jungle" src="https://sndbx.be/static/articles/writing/01_hello-internet/img/DSC_0777-001.JPG"&gt;
Road to Lacandon jungle in southern Mexico, January 2019&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="drop-cap"&gt;S&lt;/span&gt;ince a couple of months I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking of retiring from social-media platforms like Facebook, Twitter&amp;hellip; you name it. The truth is that letting them go has been quite a hassle. They have become very practical tools to keep in contact with family, friends and freetime interests, all in one place. They have also become an important source of news and information. I&amp;rsquo;ve profited and experienced them in very positive ways, however, as an avalanche of marketing and privacy concerns continues to grow, their intrusiveness has already outweighed their benefit. Added to this, the amount of misinformation imposes a high price on the time required to cherry-pick the relevant stuff. Moreover, the prevasiveness of fake news might as well be affecting us in ways we do not concioussly recognize.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going cold turkey might not be the best current solution to the social-media paradox. However, perhaps by adopting a gradual and more constructive strategy will, if not effectivley, at least more creatively balance out their requirement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog is aimed at keeping an internet presence while adding a little more custom and non-intrusive look at stuff that I like and do. I hope that by doing so, in the future I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to disregard social-media while gaining some skills at writing.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="internet"></category><category term="social media"></category></entry></feed>